本片纯属虚构。如片中姓名，情节及人物性格
与真实情况有所雷同，纯属讽刺
翻译：黑喵   校对：海参   通用语：斑鸠
（译者有话说：继续无奖竞给这个系列起个中文名
大家的提议我们都有看的，继续用力不要停）
[唱歌]今天又是义军基地美好的一天
(Singing) Yeah, it's a beautiful day in the resistance base
我要去......
and I'm just going for...
蕾伊？
Rey?
啊
Ah!
噢，呃，我不是蕾伊
Oh, uh. I'm not Rey.
你在说什么呢？
What are you talking about?
我只是随便的什么人，绝对不是蕾伊
I'm some other person. Who's totally not Rey.
好吧，你是溜进将军的衣柜里了吗？
Alright, have you been sneaking into the general's stash?
[嗤之以鼻] 没有
(Scoffs) No!
我做了伪装。你是怎么认出我的？
I'm in a disguise. How did you know it was me?
这是个伪装？
That's a disguise?
是啊，我平时会打扮成这样到处晃吗？
Yeah. Do I normally walk around looking like this?
没有，但很明显是你啊
no. But it's obviously you.
好吧，随便啦，很高兴见到你，回见啦！
Alright, well whatever. It's good to see you. Uh, toodles!
你穿成酱要去哪？
Where you going dressed like that?
（译者注：原文也吞词了）
我要去个极度机密的任务
I'm on a top secret mission.
所以，嘘，不要到处乱说......
So, shh. Don't go running your mouth--
等等，这听起来太危险了！你就一个人去？
Wait a minute, this sounds dangerous! You're going all by yourself?
你是说我不能照顾好自己吗？
Are you saying that I'm not capable of taking care of myself?
不，我完全没这么说
No, I'm not saying anything like that.
好吧。因为我可以。就只是不要告诉任何人啦
Well, good. 'Cause I can. And just don't tell anyone.
好吧，成
Yeah, fine.
我得走了，我得赶时间，所以
I've got to go. I have a very important timeline to stick to, so...
拜
Bye.
[千年隼起飞的声音]
Sound of Millennium Falcon taking off.
波！波！波！波！
Poe! Poe! Poe! Poe!
兄弟！怎么了？怎么了？
Buddy! What's going on? What's going on?
你不会相信这【哔】事！
You are not gonna believe this s***.
蕾伊开着千年隼跑出去参加秘密任务了
Rey was out there gettin' the Falcon ready to go on a secret mission.
秘密任务？我可没听说什么秘密任务啊
A secret mission?  I didn't hear anything about a secret mission.
我也没听说过
I didn't hear about it either
她还穿着一套自称的“伪装”
and she's out there wearing something she calls a disguise
其实就是一套奇怪的外套
but it's clearly just a weird outfit.
她真有危险，还不给其他人和她一起去
She is in real danger and she doesn't want anyone going with her.
哦，哦！
Oh! Oh!
啊
Ah.
我可能真的听到什么任务了，我不确定
Maybe I did hear about something. I'm not sure.
我们得跟着她
We've gotta follow her!
好吧好吧，我觉得，我认为你应该相信蕾伊
Okay, okay. I think, I think you gotta trust Rey.
这回你得相信她
Trust her on this one.
如果她在说，你知道
If she's talking about, you know,
她需要独自去，做什么的时候
she's doing something, she needs to do it by herself
你看，最好就是
You know maybe just
听女士的就对了，对吧？
Just listen to the lady. You know?
不，不，不！她这次错了
No, no, nah. She's wrong about this.
她这么离开会害死自己的。我得去找莱娅
She's gonna go and get herself killed. I gotta go find Leia.
莱娅？不，不，不，不，不
Leia? No, no, no, no, no!
不，不，不，不，不，别告诉莱娅
No, no, no, no, no. Don't go tell Leia!
[芬恩的声音逐渐远去] 我得去找莱娅
(Finn running away) I gotta go find Leia!
不，不！芬恩？芬恩？兄弟？你要去哪儿？
No, no! Finn? Finn? Buddy? Where you going?
莱娅将军！莱娅将军！将军，将军！将军！
General Leia! General Leia! General, general!, general!
对，那是我的名字，别叫坏了
Yes, that's my name. Don't wear it out.
我们得去跟住蕾伊，她要害死自己了!
We have gotta go follow Rey. She is gonna get herself killed!
你在说什么？
What are you talking about?
她出了一个秘密任务
She's on a secret mission.
我不知道是怎么回事，但是很可疑
I don't know what's going on. Something's fishy.
而且我觉得她戴了一套你的假发
And I think she was wearing one of your hair pieces.
是她拿走了呀？那个小滑头
Is that where that went? That sneaky little devil.
芬恩，芬恩
Finn, Finn!
将军！很高兴见到你！
General! Good to see you!
芬恩？我觉得你该顺水推舟。你懂我在说什么吗，伙计？
Finn? I think you outta just let things lay. You know what I mean, man?
【译者注：我查了一下，outta很罕见的情况下有ought to的意思】
我是整个组织里唯一一个关心蕾伊的人吗？
Am I the only one in this whole organization who cares about Rey?
别胡思乱想了，我们当然都关心蕾伊
Get off your silly old high horse there. Of course we all care about Rey.
（译者注：get off your high horse 停下某种（不好的）行为）
好吧，好吧。现在她可能已经在几光年外了
Okay, okay. She could be lightyears away at this point.
你有什么办法找到她呢，告诉我
How exactly do you intend on finding her, Tell me that.
你还记得她去年生日的时候我给她的那条手链吗？
You remember that bracelet I gave her for her birthday last year?
我没懂
I don't follow.
里面有个追踪器
It's got a tracker in it.
芬恩，芬恩，不，兄弟
Finn, Finn. No, buddy.
你在跟踪她(*)！你真是...
You're stalking her now. You're just full on--
（译者注：在英文语境中是非常严厉的指责，是侵犯隐私的行为，虽然不知道SW法律怎么规定了）
那才不是跟踪！我只是想一直确保她的安全
That's not stalking! I just always want to make sure she's okay!
如果你跟她说了，她也答应了
If you told her that's what it was and she accepted it,
那才是帮她保证安全
that would be helping to keep her safe
你就只是类似于 [吹口哨] 趁她不知道，塞到她口袋里
You just kinda (whistles) slipped it on in without her knowing.
嗯是啊，就是以防现在这种情况，她给自己找了麻烦
Well, yeah. For times like this where she gets herself into sticky situations
需要我们帮助
and she needs our help!
她说了，她不需要帮助！你为什么执意认为她...
She said she didn't need our help! Why are you so bent on thinking that she is--
你为什么这么......
Why are you so--
什么？怎么了？
What? What?
我可什么都不知道
It's not like I know anything.
我一点都不知道，她背着我们偷偷跑去干什么了，我是说
It's not like I have any idea of some of the things she gets up to when she's not here, I mean
（译者注：get up to 做他人不赞成的事）
我怎么会知道呢？
Why would I know anything?
好吧
Well
我觉得可能提供秘密援助并不是最糟的主意
I think maybe providing some covert backup wouldn't be the worst idea in the world.
你了解的，我们不会让她发现我们在场
You know, we won't let her know that we're there.
我们当然也不想撞破她的掩护
And we certainly don't want to blow her cover.
所以我觉得我们都该换上伪装
So I think we should all get on some disguises and
对，我们来场实地考察吧
Yeah. Let's go on a field trip.
快出发吧！全队出击！
let's go! Go team, woo!
很好。集结所有人
Alright. Gather up everyone and
15分钟后化好妆回到这里集合
we'll meet back here in some disguises in fifteen minutes.
啊，噢，不，不，不
Ah. Oh. No. No, no.
B
O
W
L
保
龄
球
入口            出口
ENTER         EXIT
GUTTER
BALLS
洗沟球
含义涉及剧透，请看完视频再自行搜索
（译者注：视频中重复的通用语不再标出）
她在哪儿？这不太对，她应该已经到了
Where is she? This isn't right. She should've been here by now.
你觉得他迟到了吗？还是说我迟到了？
Do you think he's late? Or am I late?
她可能决定再也不喜欢我了
Maybe she decided she didn't like me anymore.
希望他没发生什么事，如果...
I hope nothing happened to him. What if
如果赫克斯对他干了什么该怎么办？那个唧唧歪歪的...
What if Hux did something to him? That sniveling
蕾伊？
Rey?
[吸气声]
(Gasp)
本！
Ben!
天啊，我都没认出来！
Oh my god, I didn't recognize you!
我也没有认出你！
I didn't recognize you either!
你说“赫克斯”时候才我才认出来
Like, the only thing that gave you away was when you said "Hux"
我就想，“天哪，我认得这个声音”
and I was like oh my god, I know who's voice that is!
我不该大声自言自语的，但我忍不住
I really probably shouldn't be talking out loud to myself, but I couldn't help it.
是啊，我也不能
Yeah, me neither.
[蕾伊的笑声]
(Rey laughs)
哇，那可真是
Wow, that's
你看起来不一样了
That's a different look on you
你喜欢吗？
You like it?
是啊，是啊，很有趣。我呢？
Yeah, yeah. It's interesting. What about mine?
天啊，你看起来太棒了
Oh my god, yours is amazing.
我不知道这是什么，但看起来既亲切又熟悉
I don't know what it is, but there's just something so warm and familiar about it.
好啦
Oh, stop!
[本的笑声] 这肯定很棒。保龄什么的看上去很酷
(Ben laughs) This is gonna be awesome. This bowling thing looks so cool!
我懂！你有见过别人是怎么做的吗？
I know! Have you been watching people doing this?
我完全不知道他们在干什么
I have like no idea what they're doing.
是啊，他们就只是把这些球沿着那条小路扔下去
Yeah, they're just like throwing those balls down that alleyway.
是啊，但他们的腿总会伸成好笑的角度
I know, but they always like stick their leg out in a funny angle.
你看，我也不知道自己能不能做到
It's like, I don't know if I can do that.
我也不知道没有原力能不能玩这个，但我知道我们达成了一致
I don't know if I can do it without the force, but I know that's what we agreed to.
我懂，太容易一不小心就作弊了
I know, it's so easy to cheat by accident.
我们得像这里的其他人一样做
We need to just try to do it like everyone else.
就像普通人一样打保龄球
Just regular people bowling.
没错，没错！ [咯咯笑]
Right, right! (giggles)
你好，我们想玩保龄球
Hello. We want to bowl.
对，我们想要一条道
Yes, can we have a alley please?
当然，没问题。你们的鞋码是？
Okay. Sure. What shoe sizes do you wear?
呃，我甚至都不知道
Um, I don't even know.
你为什么要问这么隐私的问题？
Why are you asking such a personal question?
好吧，如果你想玩保龄球，你得穿保龄球鞋
Well, you need bowling shoes if you want to bowl.
什么？我们的鞋子有什么问题吗？
What? Is there something wrong with our shoes?
你是说我的鞋子不够高雅，配不上你们球馆？
Are you saying that they're not stylish enough for your establishment?
我很确定她不是这个意思
I'm sure that's not what she meant.
对吧
Right?
这样你的鞋才不会刮坏我们的球道
it's just so that your shoes won't scratch up our lanes.
你可以看到这里的其他人都穿了保龄球鞋
See everyone else is wearing them.
我猜我们得和其他人一样了？
and I suppose we have to be like everyone else?
我们才不是普罗大众！我们是特别的！
We're not like everyone else! We're special!
哦，等等！
Oh wait a minute!
不不不，我们应该像其他人一样
No, no, no. We're supposed to be like everyone else.
我们要融入，融入
We're blending in, blending in.
忘了我刚刚说的话，忘掉。不，我们不特别
Forget what I just said. Forget it. No, we're not special.
所以，是的，请你把鞋子给我们
So yes, please. Please give us your shoes.
对对，我们要你的鞋子，现在！
Yes, yes. We want your shoes now!
给你们，我觉得这会合脚
Here. I'll bet these will fit.
拿走，然后快点去8号球道。离开。拜托
Just take them and go to lane 8. Quickly. Just go. Please.
好吧，谢谢，再见
Alright, Thanks, bye!
[莱雅] 很好。所有人，各就各位，快各就各位
(Leia) Alright. In positions everyone. Get into positions.
你要怎么拿球啊，我是说
How do you pick a ball, I mean...
我不知道。这里有个......
I don't know. There's...
看！这里有些小洞洞，是要把手指插进去吗？
look. There's little holes in it. Is that where you put your fingers?
[蕾伊尖叫，然后倒在了地上的声音]
(Rey screams and crashing sound)
你还好吗？
Are you okay?
是啊，还好。没有任何尴尬的事发生
yeah, fine. Nothing embarrassing happening here.
这就是她的秘密任务？
This is her secret mission?
[萝丝笑了起来] 真好
(Rose laughs) Nice!
我是说，他真是个坏人
I mean, he's totally evil.
但他真好看
But he's hot.
听着，兄弟，我是说，你懂的，萝卜白菜
Look, Buddy. I mean, you know. apples and oranges
你知道的，各有所爱，别，别，别...
You know people like what they like. Uh, don't, don't, don't--
你们可别忘了，那个家伙想过要杀我
Do I need to remind y'all that that guy tried to kill me,
还差点成功了
and he almost succeeded!
嘿，嘿，听着。他还刑讯过我呢！
Hey, hey, look. He tortured me too!
对吧？我是说，你知道，试一下既往不咎
Right? I mean, you know. Try to let bygones be bygones.
好啊！既往不咎！
sure! Bygones be bygones!
听着，那边的，调小音量！你们知道我们得努力，毫无踪迹
Look, pipe down over there! We're trying to be, you know, invisible!
天啊！我觉得我腰要断了
Oh, my god! I think I'm gonna throw my back out.
这粉色的可真轻
This pink one's pretty light.
是啊，但这手指洞的尺寸就像是......鼻孔
Yeah, but the finger holes are like the size of nostrils.
好吧，但你的手这么大，大概可以握住整个球
Well, but your hand is so big, you can probably just put it over the whole ball.
好吧，这倒是真的
Well, that's true.
这附近还有多的吗，我也想要一个
Is there another one lying around, I'd like to get one of those.
好吧，我们为什么不干脆共用这个呢？
Well, why don't we just share this one?
（译者注：他们其实拿了儿童用球，画师偷懒了，球应该比其他球小一点）
好啊
Okay.
现在，等一下，等一下啊，显然，她没遇到任何危险
Now, wait a minute. Wait a minute. Obviously, she's not in any danger.
但我们就准备呆在这里继续看下去？
But we're just gonna stay here and watch?
你没点好奇心吗？
aren't you a bit curious?
有啊
Yeah.
你要先来吗？
You wanna go first?
[咯咯笑] 好啊
(Giggles) Okay.
好吧，他们会走一下这样奇怪的步伐
yeah. They do that little weird little walk thing.
然后
And then,
哇
Wow.
对不起，对不起，我会扔在我的球道里的，对不起
Sorry. Sorry. I'll keep it in my lane. Sorry.
天啊，我能到这来真是太开心了
Oh my god. I'm just so happy to be here!
顺带一提，你穿得像我
by the way. You're dressed like me.
我试图让自己看起来不像自己，而你却穿得像我
I'm trying not to look like me and you dress like me.
你怎么这么笨啊？
Why are you so stupid?
每个人都想去你衣柜里玩一下，将军
Everybody likes to play in your closet, General.
我回去要在上面加锁
I'm gonna have to put a lock on that thing.
听着，我们的伪装毫无作用
Look, our disguises are not working.
太多人在看着我们了。来！来！
Way too many people are looking at us. Here! Here!
我们得完全融入环境
We're gonna totally blend in.
我觉得这个和我的假发不搭
I don't think that's gonna work with my hair.
我不在意你的想法，戴上你的胡子
I don't care what you think, put on your mustache!
哦，天啊
Oh, man.
嘿，我真的觉得这个胡子和我的样子很搭
Hey, I actually think the mustache helped my outfit.
[芬恩] 是啊，的确，看起来不错
(Finn) Yeah, it did. Looks good.
[波笑了起来] 我有种想拍你屁股的冲动
(Poe chuckles) I feel like I want to slap you on your butt.
[萝丝] 想都别想
(Rose) Don't even think about it.
[康尼克斯] 你可以拍我的屁股！
(Connix) You can slap my butt!
[波]太好了
(Poe) Cool.
呃，他们在做什么？
Uh, what are they doing?
表现得像个傻逼
Making asses of themselves.
这次要不你先来？
Why don't you start this time?
好啊
Okay.
好吧，所以，拿起球
okay, so. Take the ball.
我都没带本去玩过保龄球，我真是个糟糕的母亲
I never took Ben out to bowl. I'm such a horrible mother.
我真不敢相信，我不敢相信
I just can't believe this. I can't believe this.
我不敢相信眼前看看到的东西
I can't believe I'm here watching this.
就像是有人用刀子捅我胸口！
It's like my heart is being stabbed with a dagger!
好吧，这可够夸张，兄弟
Well, that's pretty dramatic, buddy.
好吧，你怎么不惊讶？
Well, aren't you shocked?
我和在座各位一样惊讶
Well, I am just as shocked as everybody else is here.
我之前才没有看到过他们约会
I have never seen them on a date before.
我从没有，也绝对不会去和法斯马队长约会
I have never, and I am definitely not dating Captain Phasma.
[莱雅] 哦，老天啊，波！你真是不在行
(Leia) Oh, Jesus Christ, Poe! You're the worst at this!
你还是我们最好的特勤
And you were our top operative.
（译者注：经维基查证，Poe职务是飞行员，但不知道为啥公主会派他去做情报）
怪不得我们就剩下大概12个人了
No wonder there's only like twelve of us left!
[嗅嗅]
(Sniffs)
[撞碎东西的声音]
(Crashing sound)
你刚刚真的没有使用原力？
You sure you weren't using the force?
我不知道啊，我觉得没有
I don't know, I didn't think so!
[芬恩] 他们会被赶出去，那可就好笑了
(Finn) They're gonna get kicked out, and that's gonna be hilarious.
[东西落地的声音]
(Thumping sound)
我觉得我们不该扔天花板
I don't think we're supposed to hit the ceiling.
你知道他们需要什么吗？
You know what they need?
他们得要那排水管一样的东西
They need those little floaty tube things.
【译者注：像个滑滑梯一样，小朋友能在上面放球滚下去的东西，没查出来叫啥】
直接通到地上，给小孩子用的那种
that they put down in the gutters like they do for little kids.
那种通到地上的东西？好吧，我可不知道
They got tubes that go in the gutters? Well, damn I didn't know that.
好吧，你又不是小孩子，不是吗？
Well, you're not a child are you?
等下次我玩保龄球的时候，我也想要一个
I'd like to have 'em next time I bowl.
[蕾伊尖叫]
(Rey screams)
蕾伊！
Rey!
那可真滑
That's really slippery.
[波] 你什么时候打过保龄球了，兄弟？
(Poe) when have you gone bowling, buddy?
我是说，第一秩序也有这东西吗?
I mean, did they do that with the First Order?
是啊，我们一直能玩保龄球
Yeah, we went bowling all the time.
[萝丝] 我可没想过第一秩序会好到连暴风兵都能玩保龄球
(Rose) I wouldn't have thought that the First Order was like cool enough to let the storm troopers go bowling.
是啊，我们待遇可好了。他们提供最好的食物，我们还有按摩
Yeah, they treated us really good. They had the best food. And we would get massages.
呃，将军？我动议一些内容.....
Uh, General? I'd like to motion a couple of ideas--
放下你的手，波，忘掉它吧
Put your arm down, Poe. Just forget about it.
如果你真想要个操【哔】的按摩，你可以给自己按摩
You can massage yourself if you want a f***ing massage!
[芬恩]哦，他可老是给自己按♂摩
(Finn) Oh, he massages himself regularly.
我当然会，兄弟！
I sure do, buddy!
[芬恩和波笑了起来]
(Finn and Poe laugh)
你们俩要破坏我们的伪装了，嘘！
You two are gonna blow our cover! Ssh!
嘘！
Ssh!
不准你嘘我，你嘘！嘘！
Don't you shush me, you shush! Ssh!
嘘！
Ssh!
大家！嘘！
Guys! Ssh!
嘘！
Ssh!
嘘！嘘！
Ssh! Ssh!
现在，态度好点，我们保龄球玩这么烂也不是她的错
Now be nice. It's not her fault that we're horrible at bowling.
我们把鞋还给她，不要制造犯罪现场
Let's give her the shoes back and don't create a scene.
这是你他【哔】的鞋子！ 它们差点害死我们！
Here's your f***ing shoes! They nearly killed us!
本！我是说，陌生人！
Ben! I mean, stranger!
安纳金！
Anakin.
Anakin!
祝你有个愉快的夜晚，这些钱是赔偿
And have a nice night and here's for the damages.
对不起，拜！
Sorry. Bye!
[蕾伊] 我们玩得真烂
(Rey) We're so bad at this!
[本] 简直太糟糕了
(Ben) Totally horrible.
好了，所有人，好的，来，小心翼翼，不漏痕迹
Alright, everyone. Alright. Come on. Carefully. Inconspicuously.
快走
Let's go.
[所有人一起尖叫]
(Everyone screams)
赫克斯将军
General Hux!
奥加纳将军
General Organa.
你是在调查那俩孩子，对吧？
Spying on the kids, were you?
没错
Yes.
无论有什么问题，伦都会怪我
Ren blames me for everything that goes wrong,
所以如果有什么事进展不顺利的话，我得知道
so if something goes wrong I need to know
这样我才能逃跑消失，这样他才不能我身上开个新的【哔】洞
so I can escape and disappear so that he won't tear me a new a**hole.
你怎么会在这儿？
Why are you here?
[芬恩] 娱乐目的
(Finn) Entertainment purposes.
[莱雅] 没错
(Leia) Yeah.
[萝丝] 是啊，差不多
(Rose) Yeah, pretty much.
[康尼克斯] 这棒极了
(Connix) It's been great.
嘿，嘿，嘿，嘿，大伙儿
Hey, hey, hey, hey, guys.
我们在这里拖越久，就错过越多外面的东西
The longer we're wasting time in here, the more we're missing out there.
如果他们亲亲或是怎么样了呢？
What if they kiss or something?
没错，谢天谢地波和法斯马这次没出现
Well, thank god Poe and Phasma didn't show up this time.
[波] 嘿，嘿！哇哦，哇！
(Poe) Ho, ho! Whoa! Whoa!
那不是，那不是我，他肯定是在说另一个波
That's not, that's not me. He's gotta be talking about a different Poe.
没有比那次更烂的约会了，对吧？
Any date's gotta be better than that, right?
起码现在你知道性爱为何物了
At least you know what sex is now!
嘘！
Ssh!
[众人互相嘘对方]
(Group shushes themselves)
哦，等等，你听到那些虫子了吗？
Oh, wait a minute did you hear those bugs?
叫什么来着？就那种小声吱吱叫的
What are they called? They're like those little rattly noise ones.
啊，那个，蝉
Oh yeah. Cicadles.
对，它们太可爱了！
Yeah, those are so cute.
你能看到他们的脸，他们就像是在，“嘿”
You can see their faces. They're just like, "Hey."
（译者注：蝉行走前会抬起一只前脚）
你真能从怪物身上看到好的方面
You have a way of seeing what's good in totally monstrous things.
你知道，我从小就能从其他人都觉得
Well, you know. Ever since I was young, I always found beauty in things
恶心和丑的东西身上找到美
that others just thought were completely disgusting and ugly.
[萝丝大笑] 真损！
(Rose cackles) Burn!
[波] 天啊，我要尿裤子了
(Poe) Oh my god, I'm gonna piss myself!
她是不是在报复那句“你什么都不是”的评价啊？
Is she getting back at him for the "nothing" comment?
我觉得她可能都没反应过来自己做了什么
I don't think she realizes what she's doing.
我很开心，我们见面了，找了乐子
I'm just glad we got to meet up and have fun and
甚至没有提到一次工作
we didn't talk about work once!
没错，我们没有！
That's right, we didn't!
我们真会假装无事发生
We're getting so good at living in denial!
你在月光下看起来真帅
you look very handsome here in the moonlight.
你看起来棒极了
You look amazing.
你，你们有人觉得很违和吗，因为她用着我的假发
Does, does this seem weird to anyone else? She's got my hairdo on.
是啊，这很奇怪，谢谢你说出来
Yeah, it's weird and thanks for pointing it out.
天啊，要来了，她最好能喜欢，不然我的小命会变得一文不值
Oh god. Here it comes. She'd better like it or my life won't be worth piss!
上啊，姐妹，去吧，上啊！
Go girl! Come on, go girl!
所以，我们要回千年隼上做爱吗？
So, Do you like to come back to the Falcon to make the sex?
当然！
Yes!
不！不！他会让她怀孕的！
No! No! He's gonna get her pregnant!
她肯定要怀孕了
She's gonna get so pregnant.
哦，不。不，别......不戴套做
Oh, no. No, don't do it...without protection.
听着，听着伙计们，大伙儿，大家！冷静！
Look, look guys, guys, guys! Settle down!
不会有事的，法斯马已经教过他们用套了
It's gonna be okay. Phasma already told them about condoms.
啊，操
Ah, s***.
谢谢观看！
OLIVE
GARDON
Date
Night 1.0
彩蛋
感谢特邀嘉宾Bebe Drucker
为保龄球机器人献声
插曲-Bowl without Mercy
仅在Patreon下载
（译者注：为Farce制作组成员写唱的歌）
Patreon还有本视频
未删减/无码版视频！